# VALERII KOLESNIK

### C# SOFTWARE ENGINEER

I am professional software developer, specialized on C#-based desktop applications. I will ask a lot of regular and inconvenient questions and brainstorm many ideas, even stupid ones, in order to find solutions for your projects. App development for me is not just about writing some code. My general aim is to bring purpose to the product, make it precious. I put my best to each project and bring high quality and fresh look to it. I respect each stakeholder in the production chain and wait for respect to my thoughts. That is why I will be very keen to develop your soft.

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

Jul 2019 — Present (2 yr 8 mon)

Senior C# engineer

GlobalLogic

- Software architecture decisions
- Software Architecture documentation
- Configuring CI/CD with Jenkins and Azure DevOps
- Designing WPF and AdaptiveCards controls
- Unit testing
- Enrich and update product backlog
- Handle communications with client

Oct 2016 — Jul 2019 (2 yrs 10 mon)

C# engineer

Software MacKiev

- Expertise in product development.
- WCF debug and development
- Implementing new functionality over existing WinForms controls
- Integrating C++ solutions with C# code.
- Development of WPF controls. WPF styling.
- Maintenance and development of WinForms controls.
- Fixing SQL-related and C# bugs.

(2 yrs)

Jan 2015 — Nov 2016 Software developer

Upwork

- Developed high-quality desktop application with WPF technology used for automatization Skype calls through Skype API.
- Created ASP.NET Web control for displaying the instagram and tweeter feed with required css-styles and required functional pagination.



#### CONTACT

Location: Kyiv

Email: klevalera@gmail.com

GitHub: bit.ly/github-vk

#### STACKOVERFLOW





## **SKILLS**

OOP & OOD

Dependency Injection

Code refactoring

C#

.NET Core

WPF

Rx.Net

xUnit

FakeltEasy

Jenkins

Git

## **EDUCATION**

Sep 2017 — Sep 2022 PhD, Automation and computer integrated technologies

National Technical University of Ukraine "Igor Sikorsky Kyiv Polytechnic Institute"

Faculty of Informatics and Computer Technology

Sep 2015 — Jun 2017 M.Sc., System engineering and automation

National Technical University of Ukraine "Igor

Sikorsky Kyiv Polytechnic Institute" Faculty of Informatics and Computer Technology

Sep 2011 - Jun 2015 B.Sc., System engineering and automation

National Technical University of Ukraine "KPI" Faculty of Informatics and Computer Technology